Kettle and Idols
I get inspired!
I've been getting a lot of ideas from my ideas lately, especially when it comes to creating things,
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
This happened just recently,
I went to Pannya and bought a product that I thought would be nice to have,
I was beaten up.
I put it in the question box, and it ended up being made into a product,
Wow.
It was a great surprise,
It was called "Natto Curry Bread,
I made it into a special kind of bread shaped like a squid moon,
It was a miracle that they actually commercialized it,
When I told everyone that it was going to be commercialized,
When I told everyone that it was going to be commercialized, they said, "That happens quite often in spring. It's like that. In the past, too.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's what I've often heard people say,
Since we changed our name to this current team setup,
Last year, we became an independent label and established a new record company,
The name of the label is also called Wakuwaku Records,
I had just finished my MC at our 10th anniversary concert,
I was just finishing my MC at the 10th anniversary live when everyone was saying "Thank you, bye-bye",
It was the time when we announced what the name of our next record was going to be,
I said, "Waku Waku Records" would be a good name for the next record,
I said what came to me, and that's what we came up with.
Oh, wow!
Isn't it amazing?
It's okay to say it yourself. I think it's great. I think it's great.
Isn't it great?
It's great.
I didn't think it was going to be this one for sure.
I heard that they came up with a lot of other ideas, but they all agreed on this one.
But it seems that everyone agreed on this one.
I am very happy to hear that. I was so happy to see everyone's opinions unite and come to a decision.
I was very happy.
And then there are things like the titles of past live shows.Or the title of a past live performance.
I think that what I have been inspired by has often become a thing,
I often find that what I have a flash of inspiration for has become a thing.
Oh, you are the one who gets inspired.
You do get inspired, don't you?
I think that the second part of your statement, that you go down freely, is what I consider to be the spark,
It's true. It's all right.
Do you ever want to direct the group's live performances with your flash of inspiration?
Oh, but we have been doing live performances for 11 or 12 years now,
Even within the group, there are different people who are in charge of different tasks, like, "This girl can do this, so let's ask her to do it,
I was also in charge of working with my manager and the director to come up with the direction of the show,
I'm also in charge of thinking about the setlist and other things,
So, inspiration is important. I will continue to do so.
But you are also involved in the production of live performances as a person in charge of inspiration, aren't you?
Yes, I was. But I haven't said this very often, so this may be a first.
It might be the first time.
I was able to get some good information out of him. I'm doing my best. I'm doing my best.
Actually.
As a matter of fact.
I'm in charge of the project based on everyone's opinions.
Yes, I'm doing my best.
I want to keep Eve Eve and Nanako in check.
Mmm-hmm.
Presented courtesy of Kazuya-san.
I wonder if the morning flowers are blooming.